Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXXVII is arranged in 8 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXXVIII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXXXIX is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XC is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXXVII. DOMINION OF CANADA
  - Sub-Series 438-0. Dominion of Canada
    - General, 1948-1963 (Box 600a, Folder 22)
    - General, 1939-1947 (Box 600a, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 438-2. Dominion of Canada
    - Royal Commission in Consolidation of Canadian Pacific and Canadian National Railways, 1932-1939 (Box 600a, Folder 24)
    - Royal Commission in Consolidation of Canadian Pacific and Canadian National Railways. "Memorandum of Comments and Recommendations Submitted on Behalf of the Standard Organizations of Railway Employees", 1932 (Box 600a, Folder 25)
      1932 November 24
    - Royal Commission in Consolidation of Canadian Pacific and Canadian National Railways. Report, 1931-1932 (Box 600a, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 438-3. Dominion of Canada
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1931-1941 (Box 600a, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 438-4. Dominion of Canada
    - 40-Hour Week, 1933 (Box 600a, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 438-5. Dominion of Canada
    - Limitation of Hours of Work Act, 1936 (Box 600a, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 438-6. Dominion of Canada
    - Committee on Postwar Reconstruction, 1942 (Box 600a, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 438-7. Dominion of Canada
    - Wartime Labour Relations Board, 1944-1947 (Box 600a, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 438-8. Dominion of Canada
    - General Conference Committee, Associated Railway Organizations, 1947-1952 (Box 600a, Folder 32)
- Series LXXXVIII. UNITED STATES MAIL
  - Sub-Series 441-0. United States Mail. General
    - Cost Ascertainment Report, 1962 (Box 600a, Folder 33)
    - Non-Priority Mail Rate Case, Civil Aeronautics Board Docket No. 10920, 1961 (Box 600b, Folder 1)
    - General, 1960 (Box 600b, Folder 2)
      January-August 1960.
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 600b, Folder 3)
      March 1957-59.
    - General, 1955-1957 (Box 600b, Folder 4)
      September 1955-February 1957.
    - General, 1955 (Box 600b, Folder 5)
      February 12, 1955-August 1955.
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 600b, Folder 6)
      December 1954-February 11, 1955.
- Series LXXXIX. BYLAWS, DIVISION PROTECTIVE COMMITTEES
  - Sub-Series 443-1. Bylaws, Division Protective Committees
    - Tacoma Division, Northern Pacific Railway, 1932-1935 (Box 601a, Folder 1)
- Series XC. JOINT COLLECTION AGENCIES
  - Sub-Series 459-1. Joint Collection Agencies
    - Chicago, Illinois, 1934-1935 (Box 601a, Folder 2)
      1934-March 1935.
    - Chicago, Illinois. Claim of Ryan, J.C., Illinois Central Railroad, 1935-1937 (Box 601a, Folder 3)